(Amy:)So, Howard, is Stuart still
living with your mom?
(Howard:)I don't want
to talk about it.
(Bernadette:)But he's going to.
My mom got him cable!
(Howard:)In my whole life,
(Howard:)growing up
in that house-- no cable.
(Howard:)Do you know how many HBOs
(Howard:)that leech had my mother
get him? Seven.
Seven HBOs. Seven!
(Bernadette:)Long story short,
they have seven HBOs.
(knocking)
Hey, guys.
(Raj:)Hey.
Hello.
Hey.
(Raj:)Emily, you know
almost everybody here.
Hi.
(Raj:)This is Leonard,
this is Penny.
(Emily:)Oh, it's so nice
to meet you.
(Leonard:)Nice to finally
meet you, too.
Hi.
(Sheldon:)Hello.
Well, Raj,
you were not lying about her.
(Raj:)I told you
she exists.
(Penny:)Hey, I hear you're
a dermatologist.
(Emily:)Uh, yeah, I'm a resident
at Huntington Hospital.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I like their
emergency room.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, even if it turns out
you don't have Dengue fever,
(Sheldon:)they still let you
take a lollipop.
(Bernadette:)You know, Penny
just started training
(Bernadette:)to be a pharmaceutical
sales rep.
(Bernadette:)Maybe she can practice
on you some time.